<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kgraphviewer.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kgraphviewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KGraphViewer</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKGraphViewerxx</name>
  <summary>A Graphviz dot graph viewer for KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un visor de gràfiques de punts de Graphviz pel KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Prohlížeč grafů DOT Graphviz pro KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Et program til visning af Graphviz dot-grafer til KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein KDE-Anzeigeprogramm für Graphviz Dot-Diagramme</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A Graphviz dot graph viewer for KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Un visor de grafos «dot» de Graphviz para KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">KDE GraphVizi dot-graafide näitaja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Un visualiseur de graphes Graphviz pour KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Graphviz pont gráf megjelenítő KDE-hez</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un visore di grafi dot di GraphViz per KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een KDE-programma voor het weergeven van dot-bestanden van Graphviz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przeglądarka grafów programu GraphViz dla KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um visualizador de grafos pontuais do Graphviz para o KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um visualizador de grafos 'dot' do Graphviz para o KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Graphviz, bodový grafický prehliadač pre KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Visning av Graphviz dot-grafer för KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для перегляду графів dot Graphviz у KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA Graphviz dot graph viewer for KDExx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KGraphViewer is a Graphviz dot graph file viewer, aimed to replace the other outdated GraphViz tools.
      Graphs are commonly used in scientific domains and particularly in computer science.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KGraphViewer és un visor de fitxers gràfics de punts del Graphviz, destinat a substituir les altres eines obsoletes del GraphViz. Els gràfics normalment s'utilitzen en dominis científics i particularment en informàtica.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">KGraphViewer er en fremviser til Graphviz dot graph-filer, med det formål at erstatte andre forældede GraphViz-værktøjer. Grafer bruges ofte på det videnskabelige område og især indenfor datalogi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KGraphViewer is a Graphviz dot graph file viewer, aimed to replace the other outdated GraphViz tools. Graphs are commonly used in scientific domains and particularly in computer science.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KGraphviewer es un visor de archivos de grafos «dot» de Graphviz, que aspira a sustituir a otras herramientas obsoletas de GraphViz. Los grafos se usan a menudo en el campo científico y, particularmente, en la informática.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KGraphViewer on GraphVizi dpt-graaafifailide näitaja, mis üritab asendada teisi, iganenud GraphVizi tööriistu. Graafe kasutatakse laialdaselt teaduses, eriti aga arvutiteaduses.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KGraphViewer est un visualiseur de fichier de graphe Graphviz, prévu pour remplacer les autres outils Graphviz maintenant obsolètes. Les graphes sont utilisés couramment dans les domaines scientifiques, et en particulier en informatique.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KGraphViewer è un visore di file di grafi dot, progettato per sostituire i più datati altri strumenti per GraphViz. I grafi sono spesso usati in ambito scientifico, soprattutto in informatica.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KGraphViewer is een viewer voor dot-grafiekbestanden van Graphviz, bedoelt om de andere verouderde hulpmiddelen voor GraphViz te vervangen. Grafieken worden algemeen gebruikt in het wetenschappelijke domein en speciaal in de computerwetenschap.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KGraphViewer jest przeglądarką plików Graphviz dot graph, opracowaną w celu zastąpienia innych przestarzałych narzędzi GraphViz. Grafy są powszechnie używane w obszarach nauki, a w szczególności w obszarze nauki związanej z komputerami.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KGraphViewer é um visualizador de ficheiros de grafos 'dot' do Graphviz, destinado a substituir as outras ferramentas desactualizadas do GraphViz. Os grafos são usados normalmente nos domínios científicos e, em particular, na informática.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KGraphViewer é um visualizador de arquivos de grafos 'dot' do Graphviz, com objetivo de substituir as outras ferramentas desatualizadas do GraphViz. Os grafos são normalmente usados em domínios científicos e, em particular, na ciência da computação.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KGraphViewer je prehliadač súborov bodových grafov Graphviz, zameraný na nahradenie iných zastaralých nástrojov GraphViz. Grafy sa bežne používajú vo vede a hlavne v počítačovej vede.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kgraphviewer är ett visningsprogram av Graphviz dot-grafer, med målet att ersätta övriga föråldrade Graphviz-verktyg. Användning av grafer är vanligt i vetenskapliga områden, i synnerhet inom datavetenskap.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KGraphViewer — програма для перегляду графів у форматі dot Graphviz. Її створено як заміну застарілим інструментам для роботи з GraphViz. Графи широко використовуються у наукових дослідженнях, зокрема у комп’ютерних науках.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKGraphViewer is a Graphviz dot graph file viewer, aimed to replace the other outdated GraphViz tools. Graphs are commonly used in scientific domains and particularly in computer science.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Cechy:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Zooming</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Zoom</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Zvětšování</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Zoom</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Zooming</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Ampliación</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Suurendamine ja vähendamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Zoom</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Nagyítás</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Ingrandimento</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Zoomen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Powiększanie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ampliação</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ampliação</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Priblíženie</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Zoom</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Масштабування.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxZoomingxx</li>
      <li>Threaded loading of several graphs in tabs</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Càrrega per subprocessos de diversos gràfics en pestanyes</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Trådet indlæsning af flere grafer i faneblade</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Threaded loading of several graphs in tabs</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Carga multihilo de varios grafos en pestañas</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Mitme graafi laadimine ühel ajal erinevatel kaartidel</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Chargement en parallèle de plusieurs graphes dans des onglets</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Caricamento simultaneo con thread di diversi grafi tempo in schede</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Parallel laden (threads) van verschillende grafieken in tabbladen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wczytywanie w wątkach kilku grafów w kartach</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Carregamento multi-tarefa de diversos grafos em páginas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Carregamento multitarefa de diversos grafos em abas</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vláknové načítavanie niekoľkých grafov v kartách</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Trådad inläsning av flera grafer under flikar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Завантаження декількох графів до вкладок у окремих обчислювальних потоках.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxThreaded loading of several graphs in tabsxx</li>
      <li>Saving of the recent files list</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Desat de la llista de fitxers recents</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Gemning af liste over nylige filer</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Speicherung der Liste der zuletzt geöffneten Dateien</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Saving of the recent files list</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Lista de los últimos archivos usados</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Viimati kasutatud failide nimekirja salvestamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Enregistrement de la liste des fichiers récemment ouverts</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Memorizzazione di un elenco di file recenti</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">De lijst van recente bestanden opslaan</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zachowywanie spisu ostatnio otwieranych plików</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Gravação da lista de ficheiros recentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Gravação da lista de arquivos recentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Ukladanie zoznamu nedávnych súborov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Sparar listan med senaste filer</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Зберігання списку нещодавно використаних файлів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSaving of the recent files listxx</li>
      <li>Manual reload of files</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Recàrrega manual de fitxers</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Manuel genindlæsning af filer</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Manuelles neu laden von Dateien</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Manual reload of files</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Recarga manual de archivos</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Failide käsitsi taaslaadimine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Rechargement manuel des fichiers</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Ricaricamento manuale dei file</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Handmatig opnieuw laden van bestanden</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Ręczne wczytywanie plików</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Recarregamento manual dos ficheiros</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Recarregamento manual dos arquivos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Ručné znovunačítanie súborov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Manuell återinläsning av filer</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перезавантаження файлів вручну.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxManual reload of filesxx</li>
      <li>Display of a bird-eye view of the graph</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Representació de vista d'ocell del gràfic</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Viser grafen i fugleperspektiv</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Anzeige eines Übersichtsfenster für den Graphen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Display of a bird-eye view of the graph</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Visualización del grafo a vista de pájaro</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Graafi ülevaate näitamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Vista a volo d'aquila del grafo</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Een vogelvlucht weergave van een grafiek tonen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przedstawianie grafu w widoku ptasiego oka</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Apresentação de uma visão geral do grafo</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Apresentação de uma visão geral do grafo</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zobrazenie vtáčej perspektívy grafu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visar en översiktsbild av grafen</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Показ панелі загального вигляду графу.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDisplay of a bird-eye view of the graphxx</li>
      <li>Moving of the graph by dragging</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Moviment del gràfic en arrossegar</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Flytning af grafen ved at trække i den</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Verschieben des Graphen durch ziehen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Moving of the graph by dragging</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Arrastrar y mover el grafo</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Graafi liigutamine lohistades</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Spostamento del grafo con trascinamento</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">De grafiek verplaatsen door slepen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przesuwanie grafu poprzez przeciąganie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Movimentação do grafo por arrastamento</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Movimentação do grafo por arrastamento</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Presun grafov posunom</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Flytta grafen genom att dra</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Пересування графу перетягуванням.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxMoving of the graph by draggingxx</li>
      <li>Full featured printing</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Impressió amb totes les funcionalitats</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Udskrift med fuld funktionalitet</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Drucken mit vielen Optionen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Full featured printing</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Impresión de completas prestaciones</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Täielik trükkimise toetus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Système d'impression complet</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Stampa con ogni funzionalità</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Afdrukken met alle mogelijkheden</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Pełnowartościowe drukowanie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Impressão com diversas funcionalidades</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Impressão com todas as funcionalidades</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Plne funkčná tlač</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Fullständig utskriftsfunktion</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Широкі можливості з друку.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFull featured printingxx</li>
      <li>Perfect drawing of all graphviz example graphs</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Dibuixat perfecte de tots els gràfics d'exemple del «graphviz»</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Perfekt tegning af alle graphviz-eksempelgrafer</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">perfekte Darstellung aller Graphviz-Beispieldiagramme</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Perfect drawing of all graphviz example graphs</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Trazado perfecto de todos los grafos de ejemplo de Graphviz</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kõigi GraphVizi näidisgraafide täiuslik esitamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Rendu parfait de tous les exemples de graphes Graphviz</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Tracciamento perfetto di tutti i grafi d'esempio di graphviz</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Perfect tekenen van alle graphviz voorbeeldgrafieken</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Perfekcyjne rysowanie wszystkich grafów przykładowych graphviz</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Desenho perfeito de todos os grafos de exemplo do 'graphviz'</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Desenho perfeito de todos os grafos de exemplo do 'graphviz'</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Výborné kreslenie všetkých ukážkových grafov graphviz</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Perfekt uppritning av alla exempelgrafer från Graphviz</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Ідеальне креслення усіх прикладів графів graphviz.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPerfect drawing of all graphviz example graphsxx</li>
      <li>Automatically choose dot for directed graphs and neato for undirected</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Selecció automàtica de «dot» pels gràfics dirigits i «neato» pels no dirigits</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Vælg automatisk dot for dirigerede grafer og neato for ikke-dirigerede</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Automatische Wahl von „dot“ für gerichtete und „neato“ für ungerichtete Graphen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Automatically choose dot for directed graphs and neato for undirected</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Selección automática de «dot» para los grafos dirigidos y de «neato» para los no dirigidos</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Automaatne doti valimine orienteeritud ja neato valimine orienteerimata graafide jaoks </li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Choisir automatiquement dot pour les graphes orientés et neato pour les graphes non-orientés</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Scelta automatica di dot per i grafi orientati e neato per i non orientati</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Automatisch kiezen van commando dot voor gerichte grafieken en neato voor niet gerichte</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Samoczynne wybranie dot dla skierowanych grafów i neato dla nieskierowanych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Escolha automática do 'dot' para grafos direccionados e do 'neato' para os não-direccionados</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Escolha automática do 'dot' para grafos direcionados e do 'neato' para os não-direcionados</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Automaticky vybrať bot pre riadený graf a neato pre neriadený</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Välj automatiskt dot för riktade grafer och neato för oriktade</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Автоматичний вибір dot для орієнтованих графів і neato для неорієнтованих.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAutomatically choose dot for directed graphs and neato for undirectedxx</li>
      <li>Possibility to use an arbitrary layout algorithm as soon as it produces xdot format</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Possibilitat d'utilitzar un algorisme de disposició arbitrari si produeix un format «xdot»</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Mulighed for at bruge en vilkårlig layout-algoritme når bare den producerer xdot-format</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Possibility to use an arbitrary layout algorithm as soon as it produces xdot format</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Posibilidad de usar un algoritmo de disposición aleatorio en cuanto se genere un formato «xdot»</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Võimalus kasutada suvalist paigutusalgoritmi, kui see vaid tagab xdot-vormingu</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Possibilité d'utiliser un algorithme de disposition arbitraire du moment qu'il produit le format xdot</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Possibilità di usare un qualsiasi algoritmo di disposizione che produca il formato xdot</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheid om een willekeurig algoritme voor de opmaak te gebruiken wanneer het xdot-formaat produceert</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość użycia dowolnego algorytmu układu już od chwili utworzenia formatu xdot</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Possibilidade de utilização de um algoritmo de disposição arbitrário, desde que produza o formato 'xdot'</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Possibilidade de usar um algoritmo de leiaute arbitrário, desde que produza o formato 'xdot'</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Možnosť použitia ľubovoľného algoritmu rozloženia, ak generuje formát xdot</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Möjlighet att använda en godtycklig layout-algoritm så länge den skapar xdot-format</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість використання довільного алгоритму компонування, який може створювати дані у форматі xdot.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPossibility to use an arbitrary layout algorithm as soon as it produces xdot formatxx</li>
      <li>Automatic reloading with user confirmation of (externally) modified files (configurable)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Recàrrega automàtica amb confirmació d'usuari de fitxers (externament) modificats (configurable)</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Automatisk genindlæsning med brugerbekræftelse af (eksternt) ændrede filer (konfigurerbart)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Erneutes Laden von (extern) geänderten Dateien - automatisch mit Bestätigung durch den Benutzer (einstellbar)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Automatic reloading with user confirmation of (externally) modified files (configurable)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Carga automática con confirmación de usuario de archivos modificados externamente (configurable)</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Muudetud failide automaatne taaslaadimine kasutaja kinnitust küsides (see on seadistatav)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Ricaricamento automatico con conferma dell'utente dei file modificati da altri programmi (configurabile)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Automatisch opnieuw laden met toestemming van de gebruiker van (extern) gewijzigde bestanden (te configureren)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Samoczynne ponowne wczytywanie przy zgodzie użytkownika (zewnętrznie) zmienionych plików (do ustawieni)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Recarregamento automático com a confirmação do utilizador dos ficheiros modificados no exterior (configurável)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Carregamento automático, com confirmação do usuário, dos arquivos modificados externamente (configurável)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Automatické znovunačítanie s potvrdením používateľa (externe) zmení súbory (nastaviteľné)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Automatisk återinläsning med bekräftelse av användaren för (externt) ändrade filer (inställningsbart)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Автоматичне перезавантаження даних з підтвердженням з боку користувача для файлів, змінених сторонніми програмами (можна налаштувати).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAutomatic reloading with user confirmation of (externally) modified files (configurable)xx</li>
      <li>Open new instances as new tabs in the old one (configurable)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Obre noves instàncies com a pestanyes noves en l'antiga (configurable)</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Åbn nye instanser som nye faneblade i det gamle (konfigurerbart)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Öffnen neuer Instanzen als Unterfenster im aktuellen Unterfenster (einstellbar)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Open new instances as new tabs in the old one (configurable)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Apertura de nuevas instancias como nuevas pestañas en la anterior (configurable)</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rakenduse uute protsesside avamine olemasoleva protsessi raames uutel kaartidel (see on seadistatav)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Apertura di nuove istanze come nuove schede della preesistente (configurabile)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Nieuwe exemplaren als nieuwe tabbladden openen in de oude (te configureren)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Otwieranie nowych wystąpień jako nowe karty w starym wystąpieniu (do ustawienia)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Abertura de novas instâncias como páginas novas da janela actual (configurável)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Abertura de novas instâncias como novas abas da janela atual (configurável)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Otvoriť novú inštancie ako nové karty v starej (nastaviteľné)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Öppna nya instanser som nya flikar i den befintliga (inställningsbart)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Відкриття нових екземплярів програми у вкладках того самого вікна (можна налаштувати).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxOpen new instances as new tabs in the old one (configurable)xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://extragear.kde.org/apps/kgraphviewer/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kgraphviewer</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/development/en/extragear-graphics/kgraphviewer/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kgraphviewer.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kgraphviewer</binary>
    <binary>kgrapheditor</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
